Hello, everyone. And welcome to the introduction to
Houdini for effects artists. My name is savage jealousy
, and I'm gonna be your instructor for this course
. I wanted to record this video to explain the
content off the workshop and how it is structured and
how you Gates can get the most out of this
out of this content. And throughout the course,
we're going to be talking about a variety of topics
. This'll starting with the particle simulation we're going to
then move on to learn about fluids and smoke simulation
in Houdini. And then we're going to learn destruction
as well as fluid towards the end. In between
, all this were also going to learn a variety
of techniques to render particles volume and use mantra to
render geometry. No, Uh, every time we
progress, every week we progress. We're gonna acquire
new knowledge. Every week is somewhat linked to the
previous week. So it's going to be very important
to follow along consistently and study the material off every
week. Because by the time we get too weak
, five or four, if you haven't thoroughly followed
the first the beginning of the workshop, it's gonna
be hard to catch up at that time, and
the way things structured is we're going to first get
introduced to Houdini and how it works. We're going
to start slow on easy in the first week to
get everyone to the same level that we need to
be able to fully understand what's coming next. Now
I know a lot of few guys are also very
comfortable with Houdini. There is also people from a
students from the three D artist workshop, so this
the first week is going to be an introduction that
hopefully gets everybody at the same level. The most
event. The more advanced user may find it a
little bit repetitive, but it is required so that
we can make sure that everybody, including the the
newly beginners, can comfortably get started with Houdini and
don't miss on any any valuable information. So we're
going to start in the first week by acquiring how
to use the application, have to navigate through teeny
how to use opponents and things like that, and
then we're going to learn about particles, create various
particles. Now, as we acquire more knowledge,
for example, once we understand how fluid silver the
smoke's over works. We're going to be able to
create more complex particle since so at that time,
we're going to go back and create something a bit
more complex in terms off part possum on. Then
, as we progress, we're going to learn how
to do destruction, for example, and create a
lot of moving GM tree. ATTN. That time
is well, we're going to reuse the particle knowledge
from the first weeks to recreate some degrees in some
dust falling and things like that as well as create
smoke for the for the effects and on down,
we're going to learn about fluids and create Whitewater,
which is also a particle based in Houdini. So
there is a lot of intersection between these topics now
. The effects, the particle based section, which
is these guys here and there is there is more
is individual projects that you can reuse or you can
enter great in any environment. And the goal is
I don't want you guys to be re copying what
exactly I'm gonna be doing. I want you guys
to try and explore these techniques that I'm going to
be showing you gonna be. It's gonna be a
lot of new stuff and a lot of techniques that
can create a variety of different effects. And I
highly encourage you guys to try and and do that
rather than just recreating what I'm showing in the videos
, because thes techniques are very, very flexible,
and they can do much more than what I'm going
to show you. So hopefully with all these examples
, you guys will acquire enough knowledge that should buy
the end, get you very, very, very
comfortable. Working with Houdini stops dynamics rigid body fluids
as well as rendering everything using mantra like volumes and
particles and things like that. So thank you so