Hello there and welcome again and this video. I
wanted to talk about how to clean hay piles and
especially for the beginner students to make sure that they
follow certain rules that will produce clean have files.
In the end now, I started off with the
messy have filed that I myself did. And as
you can see, it's It's still quite organized,
and I'll explain, why is that? But there's
a lot off tightening that we could do. There's
a lot of cleaning and organize reorganizing that we could
do here, but overall, it's still clean.
Now the trick for this is to always use Merge
, knows when when notes can be grouped together.
So, for example, this is creating an ark
, and this is creating a pillar on grouping these
two together. And then that goes along with a
ground piece or something else. And the main structure
that I use is to always have a spine,
and you can look at you can see it here
there is a spine, and this is the same
thing that I use for nuke as well. And
this is where I learned it from because I did
a lot of compositing, and it's best to do
is find where you have starting point or whatever data
in New York the use of read file and you
start with the data and then you continue continuously plug
in data from left and right. This is a
practical for procedural modeling. It works really well.
In other examples where you have pyre or things like
that. Most set ups and stops are quite easy
for destruction. We have to use this structure.
We have to prepare and organize things like this.
And this file is quite Messina. I'm going to
show the cleaned up version of this and you can
see clearly that there is a spine. And if
there is other sections, those sections themselves will have
spine structure. And the trick is to use merchants
to combine smaller spines. And then the merge profoundly
does not have more than three unless you've really need
toe, because that's going to conclude things. Now
if something that I always do, if I need
this input somewhere here instead, off using a wire
, I would create a knoll here and call this
out and then use an object merch and give them
the same color. So this'll will be explained,
obviously to students. But when you get a file
, and especially in the beginning and there is a
lot of mess, it's best to I believe that
as it is and then clean it up. See
, that's why I don't like drug block dropped back
backdrops, Um, and and then I'm going to
use this node to, let's say, go in
here, for example. So now I have instead
of having why're intersecting with everything that will make the
visual really bad, I use an object merge,
and I know that this one is linked to this
one. And, um, and I think that's
pretty much it for for beginners. If you'll receive
a file that is really bad, it's best to
keep what they have done and then copy everything and
recreated. If the set up is quite complex,
you don't have to do the entire set up again
, just a small section so they can understand what
the process is again. I have each workshop each
of these fundamental beginning workshop. They will have enough
information in them to guide them as to how to
structure things. But this is something that I highly
encourage you guys to do to make sure that their
files are easy clean, and they can go back
to come back to it and probably work on them
. Or it's not hard to remember now, backdrops
I don't like and I'm not gonna encourage people to
your spec drops. It just used it to illustrate
how it would look like. But what I don't
like is with backdrops, you cannot expend No,
As you saw, I added note. And then
it made this whole thing bigger. I only use
flat. I never used backdrops. If I need
to name something, I would add either a backdrop
or a sticky note and give it a color if
I need to and then se test whatever. Now
, another thing that I like to do is to
add backdrops like this next to an area, and
then they create like a in the index. So
at the top, I would copy these like this
and say OK, anything with this color is going
to be pillars, okay? Or if you're working
in destruction, anything that is red means Sim Sim
note or anything that is purple. You can use
whatever coloring you need. A studios have have this
already so same that say this is out. Ah
, lot of student or most studios have terminology for
what each type should be color with with. And
that's pretty much it for cleaning up piles. They
should look nice. They should be easy to read
and have always a structure, some sort of structure
in them. Thank you, guys and talk to