Hey, guys! And welcome. So our goal
is to have 5 to 70 eights, depending on
how much we can afford and how much ah support
we need. We are hoping to expand in the
near future, and we want to start this now
with maybe for people available to support the upcoming session
, or at least the first to set two sessions
off 2020 LaGrone. We're going to add more people
, and then we're going to have a specific channel
or a specific group here called Affects Ta and under
underneath that group will have each person have their own
channel. The reason for that is because we wanna
have the placeholder. If anybody wants to ask you
something or they have question, they can, they
can do that. It will be a public channel
off course, and also it's nice to see that
here, because people will be able to say,
Okay, we have 70 ace hose online. Who's
connected? This is for journey. This is for
Kevin and or Husam, and we can tell people
can see who's online and they can ask questions.
They're guaranteed they will get support and Pete back,
and that's pretty much it feel free to use the
session, this channel to ask any question. Or
if you have any ideas on how to improve things
or if you have any suggestions. Or if you
want to mess with Igor, your role more than
welcome to do that. Thank you, guys.
And best of luck to all of us. Talk